I've got an exciting one for you today.
What you're about to watch is a special
live event that I hosted during the
launch week of the Dynamus community. A
ton of value that I've never shared on
my YouTube channel before. I'm doing
this in celebration of the Archon launch
and reaching a thousand members in the
community. So, just a thank you to you
and a way to show you what we've got
going on in Dynamis. So, this is lessons
that I've learned from building hundreds
of AI agents over the past couple of
years. And it was actually really hard
to condense all my lessons down into the
top 20 that I present here in this
event. So, a ton of value packed into
this. And so, with that, let's get right
into the event. And also, let me know in
the comments if there's any strategies
or tips that I cover here that you want
me to make a full video on. There we go.
And so, the plan for today is just to
give you guys a bunch of really
practical lessons that I've learned um
just from building hundreds of agents
over the last few years here. mostly the
last couple of years. And I typically
don't do presentation style videos or
live streams. I'm usually either just
chatting with you guys like I do in live
streams or when I'm making a video, it's
always like really hands-on, like let's
code something. I want this to be like
really practical and hands-on. Um, and
so even though it is a presentation, I'm
going to work hard to make it really
engaging for you guys. So, typically I'm
against just like showing slides. Um,
but yeah, I've got my usual mix of like
a little bit of memes and just a ton of
practical advice for you guys here, uh,
to keep it fun. So, yeah, there's 20
lessons in total that I want to share.
And, uh, the first thing I want to say
before I kick this off at all is that,
um, it was really hard to take something
like lessons learned from building AI
agents and like actually um, put it down
into a presentation that I can give in
less than 10 hours. I mean, there's so
many things that I can talk about,
different lessons that I've learned. And
so the most difficult part out of all
this is just thinking about what are
like the few that are the most important
that I can share with you guys. And so I
could probably even do like another
event just like this just sharing a
whole another set of 20 lessons. Um but
these 20 are the ones that I wanted to
focus on the most with you guys. And so
yeah, we'll just go through this right
now. Um and starting with I want to kick
this off here by just giving everyone a
quick reminder of what an AI agent
actually is. So I give this definition
in the AI agent mastery course and a lot
of you already know it at a high level
what an agent is but I just want to give
this um as a refresher for everyone. So
an AI agent is a program that uses a
large language model to reason about how
it interacts with its environment and to
take varying courses of actions to
achieve a goal. And so there's kind of
two parts to that. First we have
interacting with the environment. Those
are the tools that we give the agent to
do something like um pull messages from
a slack conversation or draft an email
in Gmail or Outlook. Like that's the it
interacting with its environment and
then taking varying courses of actions.
The thing that makes agents so powerful
and also dangerous as we'll see in a
little bit is that it can decide what it
wants to do based on what goal you have
for it. And so it might decide to take
five steps or three steps or one. We
don't know. It's it's non-deterministic
in that way because we're letting the
agent have that level of control. And so
that's an agent at a high level. And
then what I want to dive into for my
lessons with you guys today is I want to
start with u a few highlevel lessons
that I've learned from building agents.
So just kind of zooming out to the top
level of just building agents as a
whole. And then I want to give you
lessons that are specific to each of the
different components that we have for an
AI agent. And so if you've been through
the first part of the AI agent mastery
course, you've seen this graphic already
because one of the very first videos
that I have in module one of the course
is breaking down the different
components to an AI agent. We have the
agent program. This is the system
prompt, your general instructions to the
agent for how you want it to behave and
the tone that you want it to have. You
have the large language model. That's
the brain of your agent that has all
that reasoning capability. And then you
have the tools. These are the
capabilities that you give your agent to
interact with its environment. And then
last we have the memory system. So that
is both short-term memory like the
conversation history and then also
long-term memory being able to remember
your preferences and goals and things
like that between conversations and also
rag and just like knowledge bases in
general is often considered a part of
long-term memory within the memory
systems as well. So yet another quick
refresher there on the components of an
AI agent. I'm going to give you lessons
that I've learned specific to each of
these just as a way to keep this
presentation really really organized for
you guys. Um, and so then after I go
through all this, I'll I'll also open up
a time for a Q&A. Um, probably within
the last like 15 20 minutes of the hour
that we have here. Um, and so I'm going
to try to go through one less lesson
every two minutes because I have 20 in
total. So I'm going to go through things
pretty quickly here. Um, and so this is
the kind of thing where it'd probably be
beneficial to even like watch the replay
of this later if you want to pick out
certain lessons and really listen in on
those again. Um, because I am going to
go rather quickly. But yeah, the goal
with this is like even if you're already
familiar with half of these lessons and
like you already understand that and you
implement that for your own agents,
hopefully at least like five or 10 of
these are going to really resonate with
you and be useful and like I've got a
ton of really practical stuff to share
with you guys here. So yeah, that's an
overview of everything. And now diving
into it, starting with the higher level
lessons that I've learned. A lot of it
is based around the biggest challenge
that we have with agents. And that is
the whole idea of hallucinations. And I
pulled this uh this image off the
internet. I just thought it was funny uh
because it's an AI agent with a long
nose like Pinocchio. Like every time he
lies, his nose grows bigger. And I think
this is really uh this really just hits
spoton because when AI agents
hallucinate as in they make a mistake or
they just completely make up
information, they act so confident when
they tell you that information that's
just completely wrong. Like they'll even
cite sources from the internet that just
don't exist and they'll just tell you
with 100% certainty that like this is
what it used um for its information. And
so yeah, they they just seem to like lie
very freely sometimes. Um and that's
what a hallucination is. And I know that
in general hallucinations, it's a very
overused term. Um, and we hear this so
much in the AI space, but I just think
it's a good label for a lot of these
mistakes that agents and just LLMs in
general can make. And then they're also
very confident as they present those
mistakes to you. So that's the biggest
challenge that we have. And so a lot of
the highlevel tips and and lessons that
I've learned that I want to share with
you guys is working around these
hallucinations.
And so the biggest reason that we have
to deal with this in the first place is
because for the first time ever when
developing software, we have the whole
idea of non-determinism. And that's a a
very fancy word um but I like using that
a lot. Essentially what it means is
before we had AI agents when we built a
piece of software, we would take some
input like this is someone's email or
this is a request that we have to an API
endpoint like whatever that input is and
then we would always get the exact same
output every single time we run that
automation or whatever it is with that
given input. And so it doesn't matter if
we run that workflow 100 times. If we
give the same input, we're always going
to get the same output. That's what I
mean by a deterministic workflow. And
I've covered this in the course as well.
And so with non-determinism now with an
agent, when we receive a certain piece
of input, we aren't guaranteed to always
get the same output out because the
agent is giving that ability to reason
about what it wants to do. And it will
make those decisions differently even
when you give it the same exact prompt.
And so the danger with this is that it
could do fine the first 50 times you
give it a certain prompt. like you ask
it to uh research the web for something
specific or whatever that prompt might
be, but then the 51st time that you give
that exact same request, it can
completely botch it. It might search the
wrong thing or not even invoke the tool
that you want it to invoke even though
the last 50 times it did it fine. And so
that kind of brings me to the first big
tip that I have here is that to avoid
hallucinations really affecting you
deeply, you want to use AI to save time,
not replace you entirely. And so I have
this uh quote here from uh Peter Parker,
Spider-Man's uncle. He says, "With great
power comes great responsibility." So
these AI agents, they're dangerous
because they reason about how they want
to accomplish a goal. For the first time
ever, we have software that doesn't
always behave the same. Might work in
one case and then break in another case
with the same input. And that's
dangerous, but also it's powerful.
Having agents being able to reason about
what they do in their environment
unlocks a whole new level of automations
and ways that we can um improve
efficiencies in our business. There's so
many different things we can do with
agents. Uh but the the goal here is to
share the responsibility with the AI so
that you can catch hallucinations. And
to make this like really really clear, I
have a good example here. And I I did
share this in the AI agent mastery
course as well, but this is just my
favorite example in general. I always
say that like you wouldn't want to trust
an AI agent to manage your inbox and
automatically reply to every email. That
is way too much responsibility that
you're giving it. You want to share that
responsibility. And so the way that you
can do that is instead of having the
agent always reply automatically to the
emails, it can just automatically create
email drafts. And so it's still saving
you time because it gets you started on
each reply um to your emails. But then
if it hallucinates and it gives a really
bad response, like maybe it tells the um
person who emailed you that you can meet
at a time that you're not actually
available, well then you can correct it.
And so any mistake, any hallucination
that it makes is just going to cost you
a little bit of time because you have to
correct it a bit versus it would
actually send that email and um in that
case it's replacing you entirely and
then that responsibility becomes very
dangerous. So I hope that makes sense
and I don't want to just say that like
you never want to build out a process
with AI that replaces something you're
doing entirely. Um but the safest bets
for implementations for AI um for
yourself or your business, whatever that
is, is usually the ones that are going
to save you time. And then any kind of
hallucinations aren't going to like
negatively impact you greatly like
sending a an email to someone that is
just like a totally terrible thing you
wouldn't want to actually say. So yeah,
I hope that makes sense. That is the the
first one there. And then the second
lesson, again, just saying really high
level at this point is you don't want to
skimp on the planning and prototyping
phase of building your agents. And so I
covered this in my road map for building
AI agents. That's what we're looking at
right here for this screenshot. And I
dedicate two entire modules in the
course to this because it's just so
important to have a good foundation for
your agent. You don't want to dive into
the implementation of your agent right
away without knowing what you're really
working towards and what kind of tools
you want for your agent and things like
that. It's worth spending that time up
front because if you spend five hours
planning your agent, that could end up
saving you 20 hours of development down
the line. So it might kind of sting at
first like, "Oh, I'm spending so much
time not actually making something yet."
but it's going to make the whole process
faster in the end. You just kind of have
to have that foresight and and be
patient with the first part of the
process. And so that's why I cover it so
much in in what I do um within the
course and just this is how I build my
agents in general. U because there have
definitely been times when I first
started building agents that I um I
didn't do a lot of planning and
prototyping and then I just had to scrap
everything and start again. And that's
when it gets to that point where it's
like, oh, I actually ended up having to
spend 20 more hours on this agent um
because I didn't spend a few hours
planning up front. So yeah, do not skimp
on these phases.
Uh then the the next one here is to
beware what I like to call the
hallucination explosion or another word
for this is uh compounding
non-determinism. And whoa, Cole, that
those are really fancy phrases. All I
mean by this though is that if you have
many agents that are working together to
solve one problem like a multi- aent
workflow, you have to be careful about
the inaccuracies of all these LLMs and
they kind of build on top of each other.
Like for example, if you have three
agents that each individually work well
95% of the time, as in they only
hallucinate 5% of the time, the fact
that all three of them have to work
correctly for a single execution to be,
you know, quote unquote successful, that
means that your whole system is only
actually going to work 86% of the time.
And um actually, let me pull up a
calculator here because I I'll I'll do
like a little live calculation to show
you how I got this number. Because let's
say agent number one, it works
successfully 95% of the time. So 0 n5,
but then it also relies on the second
agent. Like maybe it's communicating to
it through the A2A protocol like I
covered on my channel previously. Let's
say that this agent also only works
successfully 95% of the time. Well, you
have to actually multiply these two
numbers together if you want to compute
how likely your entire system is to be
successful. But then let's say that it's
using the MCP protocol to work with some
external tools and maybe it only
leverages this MCP server correctly also
95% of the time. Well then yet again you
have to multiply 95% into this equation.
And so rounding up that's what gives us
that 86% that I have in the slide right
here. So only 86% of the time is this
solution actually going to work
correctly because even if two of the
components here are successful, you
still might have one that fails and that
could bring the entire system down. And
so that's why you have to be very very
careful with kind of what I like to call
the hallucination explosion. It's an
explosion because the more agents that
you have in the mix, the more likely you
are to have these errors kind of
compound on each other or I guess I
should say the chance of these errors
compounding on each other. And so the
biggest way to tackle this is to just
have strategies in general to reduce
hallucinations. And so this gets into uh
the next few lessons that I have here
from building AI agents which are all
about how to reduce hallucinations in
general. Nowadays when building my AI
agents, I always rely on AI coding
assistants to exponentially speed up my
development. And that brings us to the
sponsor of today's video, which is
Windinsurf. And Windinsurf has a special
place in my heart because it was my
first ever AI coding assistant.
Seriously, before Windsurf, I was
working in VS Code, no extensions like
Copilot. Windsurf has always stood out
to me for a few different reasons. First
of all, it's speed. Like you can watch
here on the right hand side in our
Cascade agent. Also, we have access to
all of the best third-party models
listed right here. And they've even
built their own. It's crazy. And then
also within their Cascade agent, there's
just so many different features that we
have. Cascade can handle complex coding
tasks with longerterm agentic memory. We
can run multiple conversations in
parallel. And they've added a new native
planning mode so that we can handle even
longer, more complex tasks with ease.
The important thing to know is that this
is not just a Vive coding tool. This is
an enterprise ready solution that's
actually already being used by over 30%
of Fortune 100 companies. And with the
Cognition acquisition, the creators of
Devon, Windsurf has gotten a makeover.
It's a lot more reliable and snappy.
They're continuing to add a ton of new
features like Deep Wiki and Vibe and
replace. And they're not slowing down
anytime soon. Plus, I am seriously
looking forward to the native Devon and
Windsurf integration that's coming soon.
I'll have a link to Windsurf in the
description. They are definitely worth
checking out. Yeah, one thing that
Benedict said, I think you can reduce
hallucinations a lot if you let another
AI check the output. And I'm glad you
mentioned that because literally that's
what I'm covering now in this in this
fourth lesson right here is the whole
idea of AI agent guard rails. And so
what guardrails are is just a piece of
logic that you have that runs either
before you call into your agent or your
LLM or after. And so then if you detect
something that is either going to likely
cause hallucinations or you you do
detect a hallucination in the output
guardrail, then you can go down this
failure path where you'd either let the
user know that their process um or that
their request wasn't able to be handled
for whatever reason or maybe you'd loop
loop back to the AI agent and have it
try to correct itself. You can take
proper course of action based on if one
of these guard rails fails. And to give
you a clear example of what these
guardrails look like, let's say that you
have an agent that is a travel planning
agent. Um, and so you as a user, you
give it the destination, your budget,
how long you want to go on your
vacation, and then the agent will help
you plan an itinerary. It's a very
common use case that I've seen before. A
lot of people build this as an example
when they show new AI agent frameworks.
Um, and so as an input guard rail, one
thing that you want to avoid for this
travel planning assistant is you don't
want to have it plan an itinerary um,
when you are extremely under budget.
Like if you want to go to Dubai for a
week for only $500, you probably
couldn't even buy the plane ticket for
that much depending on where you live.
And so that would definitely cause a lot
of hallucinations if you were forcing
the agent to try to uh, plan that trip
when it's extremely under budget. And so
a good input guardrail is you could have
a smaller more lightweight LLM that just
quickly evaluates the user's request for
their trip and determines is the budget
actually reasonable for the trip. And so
then if they do say like I want to go to
Dubai for $500, then it'll go down this
failure path where you would tell the
user like hey this is way under budget.
You've got to adjust something here um
for the travel planning assistant to
actually be able to help you. So that
would be a really good guardrail. But
then if they want to go to Dubai for a
weekend, maybe it's like $3,000 or
whatever, like something within a
reasonable range, then it could continue
to the travel planning assistant. And
then for an output guard rail, maybe you
would have another agent that is
verifying that the travel planning
assistant actually planned an itinerary
for the number of days that the user
said they wanted to go on a vacation
for. And so if they said that I want to
go to Germany for 10 days and the
itinerary was only for 8 days, well then
this LLM would be able to detect that
pretty easily. Like that's the thing
with these guardrail agents is a lot of
times they can be a lot more
lightweight. Like you could use GPT 4.1
mini instead of GPT 4.1 because a lot of
these decisions that it has to make
around like is this input or output
good? they're a lot simpler and so you
could just detect really quick like does
this itinerary actually make sense given
what the user um said and then if it is
then you return that file final
itinerary otherwise maybe this output
guardrail would loop back uh in a
failure case and have the agent replan
the itinerary. So guardrails are super
super powerful in general it's just a
huge way to reduce hallucinations and a
lot of times they can be pretty simple
to set up. Uh, and then the next
strategy for reducing hallucinations is
yet another thing that I've covered a
lot before is the whole idea of
specialized agents. And this one is
really a lot simpler to explain um than
guard rails. Because really, if you
think about it, like the way that
companies work with humans, with people,
is that you always want to distribute
responsibility between many people that
specialize in different things. You're
always going to get better results when
you have specialization, when you have
distributed responsibility among humans.
And it's the same way, it works the same
way with agents. And so if you have one
agent that handles all of your tool
calls for Slack and then another one
that handles all of your tool calls for
working with your database, you're
distributing that responsibility.
that's going to lead to a lot better
results because if you overwhelm one
agent, one LLM with way too much
responsibility, it's going to start to
fail frequently understanding how to
leverage these different capabilities
that you've given it to solve the goal
that you have for it. And so, I've
covered this a lot before with like
having specialized agents that each use
an MCP server, things like that, but in
general, this just helps a lot. And the
one thing you do have to be a little
careful of here is this does kind of
start to point us back to the
hallucination explosion I was just
talking about because now you do have an
orchestrator agent that has to make the
right call like which specialized agent
do I point to. But typically this
decision can be quite simple. So you
don't have to worry too much about that
compounding non-determinism that I was
talking about because there at least
I've seen from the agents that I've
built that this primary orchestrator
that has to figure out which specialized
agent to use, it very rarely picks the
wrong one, especially if the roles for
each of these agents are very distinct.
And I'm very clear in the system prompt
to my primary agent exactly when it
needs to call into each of these
specialized agents. And so this helps
reduce hallucinations quite a bit. And
then the very last strategy that I have
here for reducing hallucinations and
yeah these are these are all taken up in
the lessons as well. So this is lesson
number six um is examples examples and
examples. And I'll talk about this more
when I get to one of my lessons for
system prompting specifically. But it is
just so helpful to an LLM or AI agents
in general to give examples in the
system prompt. And we see this with all
of the the best AI agents and the most
popular AI coding assistants like Vzero
and Cursor and Bolt. New like they all
have very concrete examples in their
system prompts. And so like this
screenshot that I took right here, this
is an example of um it's an example of
an example in the system prompt for
Bolt. The front-end application
developer that you can use in your
browser. Um, and so yeah, like it even
says right here like example colon and
then they just paste in an example of
exactly what they'd want the bolt new
agent to output in a specific case. And
they don't hold back from including any
context. Like they have all the
nitty-gritty details of the pluses and
the minuses and the at symbols and all
the different line numbers for diffs.
Like they've got everything covered in
this example here. just showing the
agent exactly what to output given some
input that they describe kind of above
here in the system prompt that's cut off
right now. But yeah, examples are just
so so powerful and you can use examples
to tell an agent how to use tools um
exactly the format that you want it to
output. Pretty much any kind of
direction that you want to give to the
agent. Examples oftentimes help with
that and sometimes they can be overkill
like they'll make your system prompt
longer. Um, but in general they're
really useful especially for anything
that's a bit more complex with your
agent. And so yeah, hope that one makes
sense there. Um, yeah. And then the the
next thing that um I want to cover now
is diving specifically into lessons for
one of the components that we have for
an AI agent and that is the agent
program. And so again, this is the
system prompt for your agent. Um, the
instructions that you give it to
determine its behavior and um the tone
that you want it to have. And so the
first lesson that I've got for your
system prompt for your agent is that you
want to avoid adding what I like to call
negatives. And this is especially true
for longer system prompts. And so as a
bad example of prompting, you might say
something like, "Explain quantum physics
to me and do not use complex language."
That's a negative right here. Like
you're telling it not to do something.
And then a good example of a prompt is
explain quantum physics to me and use
fifth grade level English. And so in
this case in selling in instead of
telling it not to do something, you are
telling it to do something. And the
reason that you want to do this is when
you get very long system prompts. I've
seen this time and time again. I don't
really know why, but LLMs, they love to
drop the negative, as in they will kind
of like take out the do not and then
they'll do the very thing that you told
them not to do. like they'll use complex
language and obviously in this example
here it's a very very basic prompt and
and this really only applies to longer
system prompts like of course it would
listen in this case but once you have
system prompts that are like five six 10
paragraphs it will start to do this
thing where it'll drop the negative and
so you'll see something like this a lot
where like when you want it to you know
give a very simple explanation for
something you'll tell it to like use a
specific type of language like high
school language or fifth grade level
language. I'm sure you guys have seen
that a lot. Um, yeah, Benedict said,
"This behavior also refers to humans.
Humans also don't hear the negatives."
Yeah, it's true. And and yeah, I mean,
kind of like what I was talking about
with specialized agents, too. Like a lot
of the ways that we think about how
humans behave and how to make humans uh
do things well. I mean, that applies to
AI agents as well. Um, so yeah, that's a
good point. Um, and then the next thing
for system prompts, and this is probably
the most obvious lesson out of all the
20 that I have for you guys here, um,
but this is this happens very frequently
still, is you want to avoid
contradictions in your system prompts.
And so, like in this example that I
have, this is just a fake system prompt
that I had Claude help me generate just
for an example for you guys. We tell it
that it's a knowledge assistant at the
top here. And we're telling it to give
very concise and efficient answers.
But then in the very next paragraph, we
tell it to make sure that we give a
comprehensive coverage of the topic and
we include historical context and
theoretical frameworks, practical
applications, blah blah blah blah. We're
telling it to be like very comprehensive
in its response in the very next
paragraph. And this is a contradiction.
The LLM is going to take these two
pieces of instruction, try to balance
what it wants to do, and it's going to
usually just kind of randomly pick
between one of these, like either be
very concise or be super comprehensive,
and you're going to get very
inconsistent results and a lot of
hallucinations.
And I've seen this so much. And
obviously when you're creating your
system prompts, you you probably don't
want to or you're probably not going to
end up making a very obvious
contradiction like within two adjacent
paragraphs. Like that probably won't
happen. But when you have longer system
prompts and you're telling it at the
start to do something, then maybe six
paragraphs later, you're describing how
you want to take a specific action and
that's going to contradict with kind of
like the role you gave it at the start
of the assistant prompt. We see this
kind of thing a lot. And so like one
example uh of what I did, there was an
agent that I built one time that was
kind of like a customer support agent
and its goal was to get the person
communicating with it booked um for an
event on the calendar. And what I said
at the start of the system prompt is I
told it to be very flexible and
accommodating for when that user is
available for getting that that meeting
uh booked. But then later on in the
system prompt when I was giving it
instructions on how to use the calendar
tools that I had for it, I told it to be
rigid. As in you look at the calendar to
see the times that are available for a
meeting and you only ever offer those
times. You never offer times that are
outside of the range that you got
available times for. And so there was a
contradiction there. I told it to be
very rigid when I was describing how to
use the tools, but then at the start of
the system prompt, I told it to be very
accommodating to the user. And so I
ended up finding that a lot of times it
would offer times to the user that
weren't actually available. The calendar
API did not return to it. And it was
just because I told it at the start of
the system prompt to be accommodating to
the user. So as soon as I took that out
or at least I clarified you want to be
accommodating um for um maybe just like
I don't know like the like you want to
have a nice tone versus like actually be
accommodating for the calendar. Then I
stopped getting those hallucinations. it
started to only ever give times to the
user that it got from the calendar API.
So very important to keep those kind of
things in mind. So when you start to get
like really mixed results where
sometimes an agent does things properly
and sometimes it doesn't, it's usually
because of some kind of underlying
contradiction that you missed in your
system prompt and it happens more than
you would think.
Um and then the the last system prompt
tip that I have for you guys. I'm just
checking the time here to make sure that
I'm doing good. Looks pretty good. Yeah.
So the next system prompt tip that I
have for you guys is to version your
prompts. And so just like you want to
version your code so that you can revert
back to a different version of your code
if something more recently breaks, you
want to be able to do the same thing
with your system prompts. Because as you
are evolving your system prompts over
time, even if you think that you have
provided more context and of course it
would make the AI agent perform better,
you still will run into situations where
maybe your system prompt gets too long
and it overwhelms the LLM. Maybe you
added in one of those contradictions and
you didn't realize it. you'll hit that
kind of snag where you want to quickly
revert to a previous version of your
prompt that maybe wasn't quite working
to your liking and that's why you tried
another version but at least it was
better and so you can revert back to
that and then work through your other
version back in your development
environment and see if there's some
contradiction you accidentally added or
if you have to give better examples like
whatever that is to improve that third
version then you can go back to it. So
versioning is very important just like
it is for your code.
So, uh, yeah, and Jiren asked, "What
tools are you using to manage your
prompts?" Langfuse is a really good one
for sure. Um, and then also just like
having a separate place in your GitHub
repository for your prompts and just
versioning it along with your code. That
definitely works as well. Um, but tools
like Langfuse are also fantastic.
Um, so yeah, that's everything for the
system prompt. Now, we move on to large
language models and the general lessons
that I learned from working with LLMs
within AI agents.
Um, the first tip that I got for this is
that swapping large language models can
actually be pretty dangerous even if you
are swapping to an LLM that is supposed
to be better in just every way. Um, like
just as an example, a couple of years
ago or I guess whenever GPT40 was
released, I had an agent that was
running with GPT4 Turbo. That's kind of
like the last LLM that OpenAI had
released before they released GPT40.
And they they gave the benchmarks when
they released 40 and they're like, "Yep,
this is just better than GPT4 Turbo in
every way. Uh, we recommend that you
guys upgrade to this model." And so I
did that. I took my agent and I just
flipped the switch and I changed the LLM
from from 4 Turbo to 40. and things were
better in some ways, but then it started
having these like super weird
hallucinations
because different LLMs, even if it's
like supposed to be just a straightup
better LLM, they understand system
prompts in different ways and they take
actions in different ways. And so, you
have to be very careful for that. You
can't just swap your LLM, push your
agent to production with that change,
and then just call it good. Like, you
have to do a lot of testing under the
hood to make sure that your system
prompt still holds for that new LM that
you're using. Because like I said, even
if the LLM is better, that doesn't
actually mean that your agent is going
to perform better. You might have to
tweak your system prompt. You might have
to um even change your tools that you
have for your agent. I mean, hopefully
you wouldn't have to do that. Usually,
it's just changing the system prompt.
That still has to happen a lot. And
we've seen that before with other things
like bolt.diy as well. Um, and like I
think Bolt. New had this even happen as
well where like they were originally
running with cloud 3.5 sonnet and then
when they changed to cloud 3.7 sonnet,
they had to tweak their system prompt a
ton. Um, like actually more than you
would think. And so, yeah, it's really
good to just keep that in mind in
general. And then also, your favorite
LLM isn't always the best. And I see
this happen a lot. I've been prone to
this myself even where I get super
attached to a specific LLM and I don't
really consider using other ones even
though I know deep down that there are
different LLMs that are better at
different things. Like sometimes you
might get really attached to Claude 3.7
Sonnet. Like that's just your favorite
LLM and you try to use it all of the
time. And I find Claude 3.7 Sonnet um to
generally be the best LLM for coding um
overall. I mean there's a lot of debate
for that but then Gemini 2.5 Pro I find
works better for more of my creative
agents like they need kind of like
writing assistant or something like that
and so just knowing those differences of
when different LLMs work better and not
just being super stubborn and always
sticking with one like that is super
important. Like maybe you love using the
Quen models like the new Quen 3 that was
just released. Um, but you might find
with a little bit of testing and if you
allow yourself to explore that once in a
while with a little bit of testing that
mistrol actually works better for one or
two your agents for example and so then
you can switch to that for your local AI
implementation. So yeah, it's just
important to be open-minded especially
as more and more LM are released being
willing to like test those and not just
like look at the benchmarks and try to
make a snap decision based off that. And
it's easy to swap LLMs and test things
really quickly so it's worth doing so.
And then the last lesson that I have
from LLM specifically is that you want
to watch your context links. And this
applies mostly to local LLMs. Um because
especially like a lot of the big guys
now like Gemini 2.5 Pro or Llama 4,
Claude, like they all have such long
context lengths that you usually don't
hit that limit anymore. But there still
are a lot of LLMs where you do. um like
a lot of OpenAI's models are 128,000
tokens for their contacts length. Like
you can definitely hit that if you um
are retrieving a bunch of chunks from
rag or pasting in big documents. And
then local LLMs oftentimes have a lot
smaller contacts limits like 32,000
tokens. And you'll often hit those
because the biggest thing is that the
conversation history is a part of the
prompt to the LLM. And so as you're
sending in more messages and having a
longer conversation, you can hit this
limit. And the problem is once you hit
that limit, you start to lose part of
the conversation. It's it's included in
this like forgotten context at the end
here because the limit only spans this
part of the conversation.
And the very important thing to keep in
mind with this is that the system prompt
like your general instructions to the
agent that we've already covered, that's
generally included at the very top of a
conversation because it's the highlevel
instructions. And so when you hit that
context length, you'll see that the
system prompt is the first thing to go.
You start to lose those instructions for
the agent. And so you'll see this a lot
with local LMS especially when the agent
starts to seem to just completely forget
your instructions and not understand how
to use the tools anymore. That's
generally because you hit the context
length and now you're starting to lose
your system prompt. So it doesn't even
know it has access to the web search
tool anymore. So if it's not calling in
a brave anymore and you have no idea why
you're in a longer conversation, it's
definitely because of a context limit
issue. So certainly good to keep that in
mind. Um and so yeah, that brings us
into the memory systems here, long-term
and short-term memory. So I've got a few
lessons for this as well. The first one
for short-term memory is that previous
hallucinations are likely to be repeated
by the agent. And I've got another
really simple example here that I just
had Claude generate for me. And usually
it's not going to be this small of a
conversation for this issue to crop up,
but it just demonstrates it well. So
like in this case, the user is asking uh
when was to kill Kill a Mockingbird
published and then the AI said it was
published in 1962. And then you as the
user, you'll correct it and you'll say
no actually it was published in 1960.
And then you guys have all probably seen
this before when you corre correct the
LLM. It'll say something like, "You're
absolutely right. I apologize for the
error. Yes, it was indeed published in
1960."
And so then now you would think that it
would have that correct information. But
then if you continue the conversation a
while and you come back and say
something like, "Tell me about Harper
Lee and her famous novel." It might
repeat that hallucination that it was
published in 1962.
And you'll see this a lot where even
though you corrected its mistake, it'll
still repeat it in the same
conversation. And that's one of the
reasons why it's really dangerous to
have long conversations, especially in
things like your AI coding assistance
because if it understood something
incorrectly in your codebase or in the
conversation previously, it might make
that same mistake again. I've seen this
before where like there was an error
invoking a tool like the web search tool
and then later on the conversation you
ask it to do the web search again and
it'll say that it can't like it won't
even try because it just knows from the
previous point of the conversation that
that didn't work even if you told it
later that oh yeah you just did this
thing wrong that's why it didn't work.
So yeah, that's one big reason why you
want to start new conversations quite
often with your agents and AI coding
assistants.
And the next thing here, I've got the uh
prototype pulled up for the N8N agent
that we build in the AI agent mastery
course because the biggest thing that
helped me understand long-term memory
better, and like maybe this is obvious
for a lot of you guys, but this really
hit home for me, is that long-term
memory for your agents is just another
rag. Like that's literally all it is. So
within our prototype here we have the
tool for our agent to retrieve memories
and then we have the tool for it to
retrieve documents. Both of these just
using rag like you can see that the tool
is exactly the same. And then the way
that we insert memories into supabbase
is using the exact same node in n as how
we insert our documents into superbase
within our rag pipeline. And the reason
this is so important is because a lot of
these strategies that we learn for
better rag retrieval like query
expansion or re-ranking like all of
these nitty-gritty strategies which I'm
going to be covering in the live
workshop this Friday by the way. So go
to the events tab and check that out if
you're interested. I'm going to be
diving into rag strategies. But a lot of
those rag strategies apply to working
with long-term memory as well because it
just is essentially another table in
your vector database just with memories
generated by the agent instead of
documents that you're pulling from your
data source like Google Drive, your
local files, SharePoint, whatever that
might be. And obviously not all of the
strategies will apply to memories and
like you have to treat them differently
than your documents. Um, but in general,
a lot of those ways to make rag more
accurate are going to apply to memories
as well. So, really good to know that.
Um, and then the last memory lesson that
I have here
is that you want to include tool calls
in your conversation history. And I I
got this nice diagram actually from a
lang chain documentation page that shows
what I mean by this. So typically what
I've I've seen people do this a lot and
actually it's really unfortunate. The
NAND agents do this as well where they
don't include in the conversation
history anything related to tools and so
you store the human message then the
agent response and then you just flip
back and forth between these and that
makes up your entire conversation.
But really what we want to do is we want
to include everything related to the
tools as well. So whenever the agent
makes a request to use a tool like send
an email or read a Slack message, we
want to include that request and then
the response that we get back from
calling this tool like here is the
message or here's the action and the
success from that like we want to store
that in the conversation history. And
the reason for that is because a lot of
times the agent can re-reference things
that were returned by the tool calls in
a subsequent request that we have for it
in the conversation. As a good example
of this, uh we have rag. Like when you
you perform a search in your vector
database and you retrieve relevant
chunks, the agent is going to use that
to then answer the user's message. But
then the user might have a follow-up
message that could also be answered from
the chunks that it retrieved from that
first rag lookup. And so if we have the
tool responses as a part of the
conversation history, the agent can
re-reference that to answer the second
user question without having to do
another lookup. So it's just faster and
it just makes the agent more likely to
give a correct response because it's
referencing things that it already
retrieved successfully. And so we don't
have that at all if we just don't in if
we don't store the tool calls and
responses in the conversation. Very very
very important.
And then the very last one that I want
to cover here is and I'm going to give
maybe like seven minutes to try to get
through this pretty quickly here because
I want to do some time with uh for Q&A
with you guys. I want to focus on the
tools briefly here and really I want to
just dive into the anatomy of a good
tool. How you can set up a tool all the
different components and I want this to
apply no matter the tool or framework
that you're using. So if you're using
N8N or Pantic AI, Crew AI, Lang Chain,
whatever it is, like everything that I'm
talking about for tools here are going
to apply. And so the first thing is the
descriptions that you give to your tools
are key because everything that you give
as a part of the tool description is
indeed included in the prompt to the LLM
to tell it when and how to use a tool.
And so it's worth being pretty
descriptive here. And so telling the
agent like what's the purpose of this
tool? How do you call it? What are the
arguments that are here? Like for this
rag tool, we have to pass in some kind
of query so that we can search the
vector database with that query. And my
general rule of thumb when working with
tools in general is that the tool
description like what we're looking at
right here, that is your place to tell
the agent how to use the tool, this
individual tool. And then the system
prompt is where you can tell the agent
how to use different tools together. And
so that is where you kind of zoom out at
a higher level. How do you incorporate
these tools together to accomplish a
single goal? And then the tool
description is where you hone in on all
of the nitty-gritty details for an
individual tool. And both are very
important because a lot of times you
don't want to just use one tool per
execution. Like you want your agents to
reason about how they can use different
tools together. And so that's why you
want to include that in the system
prompt as well.
And then the next one is for more
complex tools especially just like we do
in our system prompts we want to give
examples specifically examples for what
the parameters might look like. So like
for this rag this retrieval tool for the
user query we're giving it some examples
of how we want to format the queries
that we would use to search the vector
database.
And so, like I said, for very simple
tools or especially ones that don't have
any parameters at all, like if we just
want to fetch the channels that are
available to us in Slack, for example,
we might not need examples, but
oftentimes they can be very helpful,
especially when our parameters might be
a little bit more complex or we're very
particular about how we wanted to format
things like our queries.
And then also for pretty much all of
your tools, you want to catch the errors
and then return the problem to the
agent. And so you'll see this in my
template that I have for module 4 of the
pyantic a the pantic AI agent for um the
AI agent mastery course. Every single
tool that I create for the agent, I
always wrap the entire thing in a try
block and then I have an accept here.
And you can do something similar in in
N8N with um the like error workflows and
for any other framework like this. I'm
showing a tool from my Pantic AI agent,
but you can set up something pretty much
the exact same in any framework as well
like Crew AI or Eggno or whatever that
is. You just catch any exception here.
And the reason you want to do this is
there's twofold. The first is that if an
agent uses a tool incorrectly, you don't
want your application to crash.
Sometimes a tool is going to fail just
because the agent hallucinated a bad
parameter. It's not because your code is
actually bad. And so you don't want to
just like, you know, crash the entire
application. The other thing is that
when you tell the agent exactly what
went wrong, and I don't really do that
here. This isn't a best example cuz I
just returned an empty list. But if you
were to maybe return an empty list and
some error message as well, you can tell
the agent what went wrong with the tool
call so that it has a chance to maybe
invoke the tool a second time fixing up
the parameters or whatever might have
caused that error. And so that kind of
just gives it another level of reasoning
like not only what tools should I call
on how, but also how should I reinvoke
them if there are any issues that come
up. It's very powerful.
And then the next thing is for your
tools. You want to be very careful to
only return what the LLM needs to know.
And this actually came up in in our
community yesterday. Someone was talking
about using the um Shopify API. Mark was
talking about using the Shopify API in
one of his agents. And for the tool
calls that invoke the Shopify API, the
results that you get back, like this is
what we're doing at Superbase. We're
fetching a bunch of records from
Superbase and we're storing that in
result here. But often times when we're
using APIs from different services like
Superbase or Shopify, what we have in
results is going to include a lot of
metadata like maybe the time for this
query or other pieces of information
that we need related to the query that
isn't like just the data that we care
about. And there's going to be a lot
more included usually. And so you want
to make sure that what you return is
just the information that you care about
giving back to the LLM. Like in this
case, we only care about sending back
the actual data. That's why I'm doing
results data and not just result. I
could be lazy and just send in the
entire result to the LLM. But if that
includes this massive JSON body from the
API with a ton of extra information, I
risk overwhelming the LLM and just
making it so it doesn't correctly pick
out of that JSON the information that it
actually cares about having. And so
that's why you want to format things.
And you'll see that as well with all the
different tools that I set up um within
the AI agent mastery course. And then
the very very last thing that I want to
cover with you guys, the last lesson,
the 20th one that I've got for you is in
general what the anatomy of a good tool
looks like. And um this is kind of hard
to see. So I'm going to see if I can
actually pull this up um within Windsurf
here because I have I have this example
live instead of just in a slide here.
So, let me zoom in on this um because I
want to just show you really quickly the
anatomy of a good tool. And so, a lot of
this is just covering what I've already
showed um for the different tips that I
have, the different lessons for tools,
but I just want to quickly like tell you
how this all applies in a single tool
here. So, this is my full tool for rag.
You give some kind of user query. It'll
search the vector database and it'll
return the relevant chunks for the agent
to uh use that to aid in answering the
user's question. And so the first thing
is we've got the examples in the prompt
and I have a very detailed prompt here
including different arguments that we
have for this tool. And then we have the
whole thing wrapped in a try catch
block. So I've got the try and then the
accept at the end. When we get an error
retrieving the documents from rag, I
also tell the agent exactly what that
error is. So the response includes the
error message itself so it can reason
about how to fix that problem when it
would maybe invoke this tool a second
time. And then the other thing that I
wanted to show you here uh for the
anatomy of a good tool is what I talked
about just a little bit ago where you
want to only return the information that
is relevant to the agent. So in this
case when we get this result from
superbase and we're calling that match
document function for rag. We are
getting all the documents and then we're
just going to loop over them and create
this string for each document that
includes the ID, the title, the URL, all
that important metadata and then the
content of that chunk as well. We don't
need anything else. And trust me, there
is a lot more that we get back from this
result object. And so that's how we make
sure that we're only giving what we
actually care about the LLM receiving.
And then we're just returning that as a
nicely formatted string. Because just
like humans benefit from having things
well formatted for them, agents also
benefit in the same way. And that's
often why oftentimes why you hear
markdown as being the best format for
agents is because markdown just formats
things very nicely. Like let me open up
a readme here so I can show you like
this readme file. Like this is using
markdown where we have sections and
numbers and subheadings and um code
blocks and things like that. Like all of
that just makes it so that the agent has
a better idea of how things are
structured. And so that's why also in my
tools I'll spend the time I'll I'll
actually code out creating a well
formatted string to give back to the
agent. Um but yeah, what I'm going to do
now is I'm going to enable Q&A. And so
I'll try to go through some questions in
the regular chat as well. Um, but yeah,
I I hope that those lessons made sense
to you guys. I hope that even if you're
like an expert at building agents, at
least a few of those like, "Oh yeah, I
didn't really think about it that way."
I just hope that that can help you um
build more effective agents. And so,
yeah, I just want to spend some time
with some questions for you guys for 10
or 15 minutes here before we wrap it up.
Um, but yeah, let me go through the chat
and see if I can find anything. And then
also you guys can feel free to start
posting in the uh Q&A channel as well.
Yeah, first congratulations on a booming
community. Thank you very much. I
appreciate it. Uh and your question, my
tools are not forming properly. There's
no syntax error but still can't get my
agent to start using tools. What might
be the problem? Yeah. So I mean this
depends a lot on what exactly you're
building with like if it's N8N or Pantic
AI. So I'd be curious on that. Um
because it yeah kind of sounds like the
thing that I have to dive into a little
bit more to really be able to to say um
because there are a lot of things that
could be wrong there. Um syntax there's
no syntax error but I can't get my agent
to start using the tools because it
seems like there might just be like a
connection error there between the agent
and the tool. Um so I guess my first
question is like will the agent ever use
the tool or are you hitting a snag there
where it doesn't even seem to recognize
that the tool is there? So I'd start
with that. hard to give like something
super concrete um at that point. Um
yeah, let's see. Fred, are there ways to
lock in the system prompt so it does not
scroll off as the context gets long?
Perhaps encapsulating the system prompt
information as memory.
So, you kind of can. I mean, you could
take the instructions from the system
prompt and just like prepend the the
latest user message with that. Like here
are some instructions. Now, here is the
user message. Like, you can send that in
as the latest prompt to the LLM. So you
could definitely do that or you could
kind of like you're saying have your
general goals and preferences and and
instructions as a part of the uh
long-term memory. So it could retrieve
that and have that as a part of the
latest user message as well. So, you
definitely can. Um, generally what I
would say though is like if you're
getting if you're hitting a problem
where the system prompt is starting to
get cut off, you're going to want to
resolve that anyway because if it gets
through the system prompt and it loses
the entire system prompt, then you're
going to start losing parts of the
conversation as well. So, it's still
going to be a problem. Like, you don't
really want to work around this issue
and and like leave the issue as it is.
definitely want to address that and
either use a different LLM that can
handle longer context or figure out how
you can make sure you don't hit that
context limit like maybe for rag agents
you'll just return less chunks like
whatever that might be I would
definitely address that as a priority
instead of trying to work around it u
but good question though yeah and then
Ryan asked do you have a specific method
to optimize system prompts especially
when switching between LLMs um and so
yeah I don't want to get into this a ton
right now but this is where LLM eval EV
valuations really come in handy. Um,
specifically LLM as a judge is a very
powerful setup where you use another
large language model to um, usually
evaluate the responses from your agent.
It can also generate the the requests to
the agent as well and be used to
automatically tune the system prompt. So
it can create you would kind of like
give it your system prompt, have it
generate questions or requests to your
agent, evaluate the output, and then
automatically tweak the system prompt
based on that. Um, and usually I find
that like manually adjusting the system
prompt is more powerful, but you can go
down that route if you want. But yeah,
usually it's either going to be like
having some sort of automated evaluation
and adjusting the prompt yourself based
on those results or just having an LLM
as a judge kind of like on either end
automatically tweaking the system
prompt.
Yeah, good question.
Um, next up,
oh, I gotta scroll down. Whenever I
click into the replies for a Q&A and I
go back out, I have to scroll back down,
which is kind of unfortunate. Um, yeah,
I have a workflow where there is a
WhatsApp chatbot using Puppeteer. Uh,
didn't provide an API key.
I use an API key that processes the
payment system. I only use the AI agent
in the conversation part of the chatbot.
the rest I set with a classifier direct
different actions such as creating a
balance, depositing, withdrawing. You
think my approach is good? Um, yeah. I
mean, that sounds good to me. Um, in in
order for me to like really like give
you a solid like yes or no, I'd probably
have to see it a bit more because this
seems like quite an involved workflow.
Um, but I guess I'm curious like what
exactly your thought is with the
classifier there. Um, I mean it sounds
good, but I yeah, I definitely have to
take a bit more of a closer look at
that. I mean, and and honestly, like you
could you could build out both
approaches because the tools will kind
of be the same. Like those actions that
you take either directed by the agent or
just buy like a separate classifier like
a um m like an ML setup there. Like you
could definitely just test both um reuse
those actions and see what works better.
Um but yeah, I mean that looks that's
looks like a really cool use case by the
way. Like that's awesome.
Um, Eric asked, "Thank you for these
lessons. Gold." I appreciate very much,
Eric. Uh, where in the community can I
refer back to it? Yeah, good, good
question. So, all of the events that I
have in Dynamus, these work or these
events and then like workshops that I
do, anything is going to be
automatically recorded and then the
recording will be uploaded within like
around 30 minutes of the event being
complete. And the way that you can go
back to that, um, actually, let me share
my screen quick. So here in the homepage
of Dynamus, you can go to the events
calendar. You can click on any past
event like I can go to the community
introduction from yesterday and then
click into it. Go to the page for this
past event and then the recording will
be right here for you to view. Um and so
that'll be uploaded within 30 minutes of
the event being complete. So very very
easy to go back through those events.
You can also go to the live events tab
and then instead of um just viewing the
upcoming events, you can view past
events and then you can also get into
that event view um this way just like we
did through the calendar. So super easy
to view those um those past events and
get the recordings for those.
But yeah, good question. All right,
let's see. We got a few more questions
here and then I will wrap it up. So it
looks like we got four more. So I'll try
to get through these four more that we
have in the Q&A. Uh, and then I think I
will call it there. Um, yeah, thank you,
Max, by the way. Appreciate it. You are
very welcome. Thank you, Andrea.
Appreciate it, guys. I'm just taking a
look at the uh regular chat quick here
and then yeah, let me go back to the
Q&A.
All right, scroll down.
Patrick asked, "With image recognition,
is there a way to use examples?"
Examples here are the attributes from
this image and use this as an example
when classifying other images.
So typically
for like an image recognition like if
you're talking about like a machine
learning algorithm or like a model that
you're custom model that you're building
up like a CNN or something the examples
would be more like your input when
you're training the model. Um so I I
guess I'm not quite understanding your
question unless you're talking about
like using an LLM specifically with
image analysis like not building your
own image recognition model. Um, I'm not
sure if you mean that example here are
the attributes from this image and use
this as an example when classifying
other images. Um, because if you mean
just like using LLM with vision
capabilities, you could definitely like
include an image as a part of your
prompt like you kind of do like like um
twoot prompting where where you'd be
like here's an image and then here's how
I want you to classify it. Now here's
another image. How would you classify
this? like you could definitely do that
just as it wouldn't be a part of your
system prompt. It would just be like a
part of your user prompt doing something
like a twoot prompting.
Um yeah, but good question though. Brian
asks, "Have you found that there is a
limit to how many agents you can have
under an orchestrator? Will it
eventually get confused?" Yeah, so there
there certainly is a limit. Um because
just like you can overwhelm an LLM with
too many regular tools since each sub
aent is essentially another tool, you
can definitely run into that issue where
um there you might have like 20
different sub aents and that can start
to overwhelm the LLM. As far as how many
it takes to overwhelm because it's
usually pretty simple like here is your
Slack agent, here's your data analytics
agent, here's your database agent. like
it's usually pretty easy for the
orchestrator to know when to call into
each of them. You can go pretty far.
Like you can have a good number of sub
aents under the orchestrator. Um like
I've seen as many as like 15 to 20 and
like it still works really well because
usually that handoff is just really
really simple. Um but like if you really
want to get fancy, you can start to have
like an orchestrator that has sub
orchestrators. Um I don't find that to
be necessary like ever. Um, but you
definitely could do that if you just
want to like kind of create this
hierarchy of agents to like really make
sure that you never have more than 10
tools for any given agent or whatever
that might be. Um, but yeah, usually I
don't find this to be an issue because
if you have an agent that you actually
want to orchestrate like 50 different
sub aents, you've probably got more of a
problem there where you're just trying
to do too much with one application and
you might want to split that into
different things in the first place as
like entirely separate applications.
Yeah, good question.
All right, next one. Is there a video in
the community for vibe coding full stack
app in Pantic AI? Any vibe coding for a
serverless app? Yeah, so as one of the
videos in module four in the AI agent
mastery course, I talk about using AI
coding assistance to help us build
agents with Pyantic AI. And I and I will
say that I I don't generally condone
vibe coding overall. like I don't want
to uh I don't want you to trust the LLM
entirely when coding things. I want you
to be able to validate its output. Um
but certainly using AI coding assistance
is a big thing that I focus on for at
least kind of getting that first 90% of
the code created and then then you just
perfecting it and fixing any errors that
come up yourself. And then as far as
vibe coding um a full stack app, that is
something I'll cover more in module five
of the AI agent mastery course when I
build a full application around the
agent that we built in the previous
modules. And then for serverless, um I
will be covering serverless for
deploying agents in module six.
And so all that is coming soon. I want
to get these modules out for you guys as
soon as possible.
Um is there a support for calendarly
one-on-one session with colon team for
query features or client requests? Yeah,
good question. So, I'll be having um
generally three office hour sessions a
week, which aren't going to be
one-on-one sessions um because obviously
there's just like so many different
questions that all you guys have,
fantastic questions, but I got to be
able to address um you know, a lot of
people at the same time. And so, I I
won't be offering one-on-one sessions,
but the office hours are going to be
your place to come in with specific
questions on your projects or like when
you want to just get into the
nitty-gritty details of things like
that's what I'm going to be offering.
And I'm specifically offering many of
those every single week just to make
sure that there's so much time available
for that that it's not going to be like
50 people coming into each office hour.
It's going to be a very small group of
people and we can all learn together at
the same time as we're going through
these questions as well. They can all be
recorded sessions.
Um yeah, then the last question that we
have here and then I'll close it off for
all of us. Got one from Tom. Um let's
see. Let me got to scroll back down. All
right. So Tom asked, "What are your
thoughts about process the process of
fine-tuning embedding models? I feel
like this is an important building block
for accurate responses from rag. Maybe
you could visit this one of your
videos." Yeah, absolutely. Great
question. Fine-tuning embedding models
is super super powerful and definitely
something that I've been wanting to
cover on my channel for a while. The
biggest problem is it's a bit more
involved than a lot of the things I like
typically cover on my channel. So, it's
just a it's a hard video to create and
it's it's not going to be as easy for
people to like resonate with that really
quick like, oh yeah, I'm going to like
go use this in N right now because it's
not that simple. Um, but it is super
super important and specifically I am
going to be creating a course on
knowledgebased agents like a rag
specific course for Dynamis um sometime
after the AI agent mastery course and
fine-tuning embedding models is going to
have a dedicated portion of that course
for sure because it's super important.
Um, so yeah, really good question.
And yeah, something I definitely want to
focus on.
Oh, and then yeah, really quick one from
David. If we've made changes to your
repo, how can we submit them? You can
make a poll request in any repo in the
Dynamus organization if you want. And
so, yeah, right now the AI agent mastery
repo is the only one that we have. Um,
so yeah, definitely feel free to make a
PR if you fix something up or just have
a new feature. I'll take a look and I'll
be pretty picky about the things that I
add into the repo. But yeah, I mean, if
there's like an issue that's like
seriously needs to be addressed or
something that I can add into the
package without having to redo a bunch
of videos or anything, then yeah, I'm
all yours for that. Um, so yeah, good
questions. And um, let me remove that
there. I'm going to go back to the chat.
Uh, Jiren said, "Man, such good content.
I appreciate it very much."
Uh, yeah, Pan said, "Vive coding is 90%
code in the future, so I believe having
personalized coding agents should be a
great add-on." Yeah, definitely.
Definitely.
Um, Aiden said, "Appreciate the help and
knowledge you give." Yeah, thank you
very much. I'm glad I'm glad that this
has been helpful for you guys. Um, and
yeah, with that, I'm generally going a
little bit over in these events, but I
just love answering all your guys'
questions, and I appreciate them a ton.
And thank you all for being here and
just hearing me out on all the lessons
that I've learned, at least a good chunk
of lessons that I've learned from
building agents over the years. So, I
hope that was super helpful for you
guys. And of course, if you have any
questions on any of those lessons and
you want me to elaborate on anything,
like please ask away in the community,
come to office hours next week with
questions. Um, I'd love to help address
anything more that you guys are curious
about and specifically like how you can
apply these lessons into your projects.
I know that there's probably a lot of
questions about that kind of stuff and
so I'd love to get into the details of
that with you as well. So, that is
everything that I have for today. Thank
you all for being here, for coming with
such great questions as well. And I will
see you guys around in the community.